http://www.tearfilm.org/paginalong-privacy/6031_1/eng/

membership
sign up!
MEMBERSHIP
SIGN UP!
CONFERENCES
UNIQUE CHALLENGES AND UNMET NEEDS FOR THE MANAGEMENT OF OCULAR SURFACE DISEASES THROUGHOUT THE WORLD
EUROPEAN TFOS AMBASSADOR MEETING
THE 8TH INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON THE TEAR FILM & OCULAR SURFACE: BASIC SCIENCE AND CLINICAL RELEVANCE
THE 7TH INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON THE TEAR FILM & OCULAR SURFACE: BASIC SCIENCE AND CLINICAL RELEVANCE
ABSTRACT BOOKS
THE 6TH INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON THE TEAR FILM & OCULAR SURFACE: BASIC SCIENCE & CLINICAL RELEVANCE
THE 5TH INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON THE TEAR FILM & OCULAR SURFACE: BASIC SCIENCE & CLINICAL RELEVANCE
REPORTS
A LIFESTYLE EPIDEMIC: OCULAR SURFACE DISEASE GLOBAL TASKFORCE TO ADDRESS VISION-COMPROMISING CHALLENGES
TFOS EUROPEAN AMBASSADOR MEETING: UNMET NEEDS AND FUTURE SCIENTIFIC AND CLINICAL SOLUTIONS FOR OCULAR SURFACE DISEASES
TFOS DEWS IIÂ® REPORT
TFOS INTERNATIONAL WORKSHOP ON CONTACT LENS DISCOMFORT (CLD)
TFOS CLAES DOHLMAN CONFERENCE AWARD WINNERS
GORDON RESEARCH CONFERENCE: THE BIOLOGY AND PATHOBIOLOGY OF THE CORNEA
TFOS CONFERENCE AWARDS
PATIENTS
SPONSORS
VISION LOUNGE
WHAT IS A TFOS VISION LOUNGE?
JOIN THE 1ST TFOS VISION LOUNGE IN BOSTON!
privacy
INFORMATION FOR THE USE OF PERSONAL DATA
In accordance with the 2016/679 European Regulation
(This Policy was updated on May 23rd, 2018 in accordance to the regulations set by the General Data Protection Regulation - GDPR)
Owner and Manager
The holder of the processing of personal data is the Tear Film & Ocular Surface Society (TFOS), with registered office in Boston, MA, USA.
The Data Processor is Amy Gallant Sullivan, domiciled for this office at the TFOS headquarters, PO BOX 130146, located in Boston, MA, US, email address: privacy@tearfilm.org
Purpose of the treatment
Data is collected and kept for the fulfillment of tax obligations, for the management and organization of activities carried out by TFOS and for communications regarding institutional activities that we have planned and carried out.
In detail:
• the administrative management of the members
• information about initiatives, activities and projects carried out by or in collaboration with TFOS
TFOS collects personal data such as: name, surname, telephone, mobile phone, address, email, and other information provided voluntarily by the interested parties. To carry out tax obligations, TFOS may also collect tax data of the interested parties (tax code, place and date of birth).
TFOS guarantees that processing using electronic means is carried out by minimizing the use of personal and identification data, limiting the use of cases in which it is strictly necessary for the achievement of the purposes for which the data was collected.
Method of treatment
All activities concerning treatment of data are performed through traditional and electronic communication tools such as: emails, newsletters, phone calls, social networks.
The processing of data is carried out in compliance with current regulations, by means of paper and IT tools suitable to protect your security and confidentiality, in compliance with the measures set forth in the 2016/679 European Regulation, and relate to organizational, technical and logistical aspects.
This treatment consists of the collection, registration, organization, storage, consultation, processing, extraction, selection, comparison, use, cancellation and destruction of the data. The processing operations indicated above are carried out exclusively by TFOS in relation to the purposes for which the data was collected, through internal staff in charge of the various services related to the above.
The consent to the processing of data is optional, but in absence of this, the holder cannot manage requests regarding established institutional relationship (e.g. registration to events, subscription to the newsletter, etc.).
TFOS does not provide the aforementioned personal data to third parties for advertising purposes, does not sell them or lease them to third parties. In addition, it will not give, the personal data of its members to unauthorized third parties. The duration of the treatment is functional to the relationship with TFOS and to the administrative, accounting and organizational obligations. Data is in any case kept for a period of fifteen years for the purposes of traceability of the provided services and for internal administrative provisions and for the verification of related tax and compliance obligations.
Who treats the data
Personal data will be accessible to the TFOS organization, formally appointed as persons in charge.
The eventual forwarding to and use of personal data by external individuals and organizations acting on behalf of TFOS are governed by contracts that provide for an adequate level of protection of personal data. Users' personal data will only be used and released by TFOS exclusively to individuals and organizations working on their own behalf, in accordance with this Privacy Policy and as expressly provided for by current legislation.
Specifically, data can be made available to third party suppliers, which carry out essential processing activities for the TFOS activity, some of which reside in foreign countries.
These third parties will act as autonomous data controllers, solely and exclusively to satisfy the request of the interested party (e.g. personal data communicated to third party suppliers for sending the newsletter, insertion in the database), or to which data communication is necessary to comply with the law or regulations (administrative obligations), or to organize and coordinate particular initiatives promoted by TFOS.
TFOS constantly monitors the activities commissioned to these third parties, verifying the work and reliability in terms of privacy.
With regard to the provision of data through our pages on social networks (Facebook, Twitter, etc ...), TFOS takes all measures in its possession to ensure secure treatment; these measures are however conditioned by the nature of the instrument itself, its usability by the user and the actions in terms of privacy undertaken directly by the owner of the social network.
TFOS cannot be held responsible for untruthful information sent directly by an interested party (e.g. personal data, postal addresses, email address), and which may possibly involve unaware third parties. Upon the occurrence of such incidents, TFOS will intervene promptly to protect the privacy of the interested parties involved, reserving the right to denounce such fraudulent actions to the competent authorities.
Cookies
The TFOS site may use technical cookies, the use of which does not require the user's consent, as they guarantee normal navigation and use of the website and are necessary to allow a safe and efficient navigation of the site.
We also use additional cookies through Google Analytics. Google Analytics is a Web statistics service offered by Google, Inc. that uses cookies to analyze and create reports on the use of our site by users. It is widely used on the Web and uses anonymous data, i.e. cookies do not include personal information that allows users to be identified. These cookies help us to understand the behavior of our visitors and allow us to make improvements to make their experience more enjoyable.
Visitors can choose not to participate in Google Analytics using this browser add-on.
Rights of interested users
TFOS guarantees to each person concerned, the exercise of their rights as set out in Chapter III of the General Data Protection Regulation:
• access to personal data as well as to know the logic and the purposes on which the treatment with electronic tools is based
• to obtain the updating, correction or cancellation of the same or the limitation of processing
• to obtain anonymous data transformation or blocking of data
• to oppose the treatment
• to oppose data portability
• to revoke the consent, where provided: the withdrawal of consent does not affect the lawfulness of the treatment based on the consent granted before the revocation
• to propose a complaint to the supervisory authority
The subjects to whom the personal data refer will be able to exercise the relative rights by contacting the owner at the above address or e-mail address privacy@tearfilm.org or Tear Film & Ocular Surface Society, PO BOX 130146, Boston, MA, 02113, USA
09 DecemberA LIFESTYLE EPIDEMIC: OCULAR SURFACE DISEASE - Global Taskforce To Address Vision-Compromising Challenges
Today the Tear Film & Ocular Surface Society (TFOS), a world leader in eye health research and education, announced their next global Workshop, entitled “A Lifestyle Epidemic: Ocular Surface Disease."
The World Health Organization indicates that eye problems are increasingly linked...
20 NovemberPublished! TFOS European Ambassador meeting: Unmet needs and future scientific and clinical solutions for ocular surface diseases
The mission of TFOS is to advance the research, literacy & educational aspects of the scientific field of the tear film & ocular surface. TFOS Ambassadors are dynamic & proactive experts, who help promote TFOS initiatives throughout the world & identify unmet needs & propose future...
Tweets by Eyeppl
Corporate Advisory Board Members
Questo sito utilizza cookie di profilazione propri e di siti terzi. Se vuoi saperne di più consula la cookie policy. Chiudendo questo banner acconsenti all'uso dei cookie. GrazieOkLeggi di più
